nubella.com 2009-12-19

# Nubella - Privacy Statement

We’re very aware of the need to respect, and protect the privacy of all our readers. We’ve built a site that gives you the power to control how much information you give to us, and how that information is used.

Please read this Policy carefully. Should you have any questions about this Policy or our data collection, use or disclosure practices, please contact us in any of the ways listed at the end of this Policy. Please also be sure to read our complete [Terms of Use](http://www.nubella.com/mambots/editors/tinymce/content/view/2366/330/), of which this Privacy Policy is a part.

This privacy policy ("Policy") discloses the data collection, use and disclosure practices of Marketing Technology Solutions, Inc. and its subsidiary, Nubella (collectively referred to herein as "Nubella"), in connection with the web site, [www.Nubella.com](http://www.nubella.com/) (the "Web Site" or “Site”). Because this Policy pertains to information collected only directly through or from the Site, this Policy does not apply to personal information collected from offline resources and communications (for instance, if you send us a postal letter or give us a phone call). This Policy also does not apply to third party online resources to which Nubella websites may link, where Nubella does not control the content or the privacy practices.

**WHAT IS PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

The term "personal information" as used in this Policy means any information or set of information that identifies an individual.

**WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

Since Nubella’s purpose is to provide you with detailed health and wellness information, we may request correspondingly detailed personal information. Certain information that we request is necessary for us to provide one or more Nubella services to you. Other information is optional. However, if you elect not to provide this optional information, this choice may limit the value of the Nubella experience for you. For example, if we do not have your dietary preferences, we will not be able to provide the most suitable information and recipes. As you can see, the more information we have about you, the more valuable the Nubella experience can be for you.

Nubella may collect or track the e-mail addresses of visitors that communicate with the Site via e-mail and information knowingly provided by the visitor in online registration forms, information requests, the “Contact Us” section of the Site, and other online resources. We collect personal information through our registration form and also from registration information you provide to our marketing partners (for users that join Nubella though one of our partners). Information collected at registration includes, but is not limited to, name, address, email address, gender and birth date. You may choose to provide additional information, including (but not limited to) such health and lifestyle information about you and your family as marital status and household information (spouse, children, pets, etc.); ethnicity; education; income; occupation; purchasing habits; reading habits; insurance; height; weight; physical and mental health conditions and diseases; symptoms; treatments; medications; medical devices; vitamins; health habits; and participation in research surveys and clinical trials. Generally, in addition to the other uses and features described in this Privacy Policy, we use this information to improve your Nubella experience by tailoring the content displayed in your version of the Site to the information that we describe in this paragraph.

In addition, we might receive information about you from outside sources and add it to your Nubella membership information. We do this to improve personalization of our services (for example, providing better newsletter content, advertising or special offers that we think will interest you). We also may compare our customer list to lists received from other companies, in an effort to avoid sending identical messages to our members.

Even if you do not register with Nubella, we collect or track non-personal information including (1) the home server domain names, e-mail addresses, type of client computer, files downloaded, search engine used, operating system, and type of Web browser of visitors to the Site, and (2) aggregate and user-specific information regarding which pages Site visitors access, using tracking technologies, such as action tags or [cookies](http://www.nubella.com/content/view/1786/79/#cookies).

You may request your removal from our database at any time. Please see “[Changing Your Status](http://www.nubella.com/content/view/1786/79/#changingStatus),” below, for details.

**HOW WE USE THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

We may use information collected for many reasons, including:

  * to provide you with personalized information via electronic delivery and/or direct mail; 
  * to send you targeted advertising via electronic delivery and/or direct mail;
  * to contact you for feedback and surveys via electronic delivery and/or direct mail;
  * to send you general and administrative information about your Nubella membership via electronic delivery and/or direct mail;
  * for product development;
  * to improve the content and layout of the Site;
  * to statistically analyze user behavior;
  * for editorial and feedback purposes;
  * to contact Site visitors regarding account status and changes to the Terms and Conditions, Privacy Statement, Terms of Use and other policies and agreements; and
  * to provide your contact information to Nubella marketing partners whose offer(s) you have selected to receive in order for them to send you those offer(s) via electronic delivery, telemarketing and direct mail. Please note that these partners will be instructed to contact you only if you request them to do so

We do not send or support the delivery of unsolicited bulk e-mail (a.k.a. “spam").

While Nubella may undertake efforts to see that any third party to which Nubella shares, rents, sells, or otherwise discloses personal information is under a contractual obligation to use the personal information solely for the purposes for which the information was disclosed, such third parties are independent third parties over which Nubella exercises no control. Nubella is not responsible for, and will not be liable for, their conduct, actions, omissions, or information handling or dissemination practices.

**Market Research**

You may choose to participate in market research activities through Nubella, including health panels and surveys. When participating in such activities, we may ask you to submit personal information. We may combine the personal information you provide to us with research tools and information from other sources, including prescription information. We use this information to perform research, and to prepare reports and analyses for our clients. _Our reports and analyses to clients are made only on an anonymous basis_. Our clients never see any single individual's personal information and we will not use the personal information you provided during market research activities to advertise, promote, or market goods or services to you. 

**Third-party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web Site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. It is solely the visitors’ obligation to review and understand the privacy practices and policies of these other websites and of these advertisers and third parties. These companies are independent third parties over which Nubella exercises no control. Nubella is not responsible for, and will not be liable for, their conduct, actions, omissions, or information handling or dissemination practices. 

**Cookies**

Nubella may place “cookies” on your hard drive. Internet cookies are small text files that save data about individual visitors, save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit the Web Site, and help us to deliver personalized content and other services. Many Web browsers are automatically set to accept cookies. _You may change your browser settings to either reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is about to be placed on your computer_. Please note, however, that rejecting cookies while visiting the Web Site may result in certain parts of the Web Site not operating correctly or as efficiently as if they were allowed. For example, if you are a Nubella member, you may need to enter your username and password each time you visit the Web Site. 

If we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf, these companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Those are standard measures that are used on most Web sites. _These third-party advertising cookies and action tags generally do not associate your name with any data that they gather_. Please note that these companies are independent third parties over which Nubella exercises no control. Nubella is not responsible for, and will not be liable for, their conduct, actions, omissions, or information handling or dissemination practices. 

**E-mail Links**

In some instances we may include certain links in our e-mails that will allow us to monitor whether you access specific content or advertisements contained in that e-mail. When you click on one of these links, we will record that click and certain activities on the Web page associated with that link. We may use this information for various purposes, such as to conduct internal research on our users' demographics, interests, and behavior in and to our e-mail advertisements and content. We also use it to customize the content displayed on your version of Nubella, tailoring it to your interests.

**Disclosures We Must Make for Legal Reasons**

Nubella may disclose information about you and your use of the Nubella Web Site and the Nubella services if Nubella believes such disclosure is reasonably necessary: (i) to comply with the law or legal process; (ii) to protect or defend the rights or property of Nubella or others; (iii) to enforce the Nubella Terms and Conditions or this Privacy Policy; and (iv) to respond to claims that the content(s) of a communication violates the rights of another. Also, circumstances may arise where, for business reasons, Nubella may decide to reorganize, or divest all or part of its business through sale, assignment, merger or acquisition. In these circumstances, personal information may be shared with the actual or prospective purchasers or assignees.

**Reports**

We periodically prepare analyses and reports reflecting visitor and member use of the Nubella Web Site and Nubella services for our internal use as well as for a limited number of our business partners. These reports include aggregate information about Nubella members, and in certain instances, visitors to the Nubella Web Site. _The information in these reports will not identify you individually_. Our business partners who have access to these reports will not be able to contact you from the information contained in the reports. 

**Referral Program**

As part of our referral program, you can provide contact information (such as name and e-mail address) of your friends and family whom you think would like to receive Nubella e-mails and use the Nubella services. The users referred to us receive sample Nubella e-mails, but do not become members until they confirm their interest in the service.

**Give-Aways and Contests**

We may conduct give-aways, contests and other promotions on the Nubella Web Site in which we may ask you for additional information. We use and treat this information in accordance with the terms of this Policy. Participation in such give-aways and contents is not necessary to use Nubella, and you may choose whether you wish to participate in any particular give-away or contest.

**SECURITY**

_The Web Site has implemented extensive security measures in place intended to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under its control_. Our hardware infrastructure is housed in a controlled access facility that restricts access to authorized individuals with positive identification. Our network access to the infrastructure is protected by a firewall protection system. Member information is backed up on a periodic basis to protect against accidental loss. When you enter personally identifiable information—e.g. registration, health profile questions, surveys—we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption to protect your information during its transmission across the Internet. We use VeriSign digital ID to assist you with verification that you’re actually using Nubella.com, and have not been diverted to a fake site by hackers. We restrict the access of our staff and contractors to your information. Third-party marketing partners receive your information only under the substantial restrictions, imposed by you and/or us, described elsewhere in this Policy. Our offices are protected with a key-card entry system, security guards, and other measures.

However, we cannot guarantee that communications between you and Nubella will not be intercepted by others and that information stored on our servers will be free from unauthorized access. While we have taken reasonable precautions to protect this information, you should always use discretion in what information you send to us and not expect that such information will be absolutely free from intrusion. The confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to or from Nubella via this Web Site or via e-mail cannot be and is not guaranteed. Accordingly, Nubella is not responsible for the security of information transmitted via the Internet.

If you prefer not to communicate with us via e-mail or the Internet, you can contact us by telephone at 1 (732) 452-9797; by fax at 1 (201) 332-3283; or by postal mail at 10 Exchange Place, 24th Floor, Jersey City, NJ 07302, USA.

Please note that _Nubella does not request personal information by sending e-mails. We only collect such information on our website_. If you receive an e-mail purporting to be from us that solicits personal information, do not respond to it. Instead, please contact our security staff [info@mateso.com](mailto:info@mateso.com) immediately.

**CHILDREN**

Nubella services and websites are not directed at children and are designed for individuals who are 18 years of age or older. This Site must not be used by children under 13. Children under 13 must not submit personal information. To register for a Nubella.com account, you must certify that you are at least 13 years of age. Registrants under the age of 13, when detected, are summarily banned from Nubella. We will not request or knowingly collect information from an individual under 13 years of age. 

**LINKS**

The Nubella Web Site, as well as the electronic messages sent as part of the Nubella Service, may contain links to other sites or services. Nubella is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party sites. If you have a question about the privacy policy of those other sites, please contact them directly.

**CHANGING YOUR STATUS**

As a convenience to our members, we provide a number of different opportunities to review and change information in your profile and to unsubscribe from the Nubella service. For example, you can go to the Web Site and log into your profile page to make any desired changes. Similarly, each e-mail message you receive from us will contain one or more links to the Web Site that allow you to conveniently access this information. Or, you can unsubscribe at any time by [clicking here](mailto:info@mateso.com).

To request that your information that has been voluntarily provided to Nubella through registration, online forms, customer orders, or electronic information subscription be removed, from our database, send an e-mail request to [info@mateso.com](mailto:info@mateso.com). We will attempt to delete such information, where feasible, after we receive a request from you to delete information. At the current time, we are not able to offer users the ability to delete all information from our database. Please be advised that by requesting that your data be removed from our database, you will be unsubscribed from the Nubella services.

**UPDATES**

Nubella reserves the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, update, change, modify or revise this Privacy Policy or our services simply by posting such change, update or modification on the Web Site. Any such addition, update, change, modification or revision will be effective immediately upon posting on the Web Site. Upon any change to this Privacy Policy or our services, we may also notify you via e-mail.

If you do not accept the terms of this Policy, we ask that you do not register with Nubella, or alternatively, [click here](mailto:info@mateso.com) to unsubscribe.

Nubella is offered by Marketing Technology Solutions Inc., Jersey City, New Jersey, USA.

**CONTACT US**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this Web Site, or your dealings with this Web Site, you can contact: 

Marketing Technology Solutions Inc.  
10 Exchange Place, 24th Floor  
Jersey City, NJ 07302 USA  
1 (732) 452-9797  
Unsubscribe: [Click here](mailto:info@mateso.com) to unsubscribe.  
Contact Us: [info@mateso.com](mailto:info@mateso.com)
